[{"question": "How much does a new Audi R8 GT Coupe cost?", "answers": ["$201000", "$253000", "$150000", "$325000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}, {"question": "What would you have to pay for an iPhone 15?", "answers": ["$1100", "$1600", "$900", "$2000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 0}, {"question": "How much is a pair of Air Force 1's?", "answers": ["$100", "$145", "$95", "$115"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 3}, {"question": "As of today (11/4-2024), how much is a TESLA stock worth?", "answers": ["$192.35", "$171.76", "$153.62", "$164.22"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}, {"question": "What is the median listing home price in Beverly Hills LA?", "answers": ["$8.8M", "$10.6M", "$4.2M", "$24.5M"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 0}, {"question": "How much does a cinema ticket cost (in Sweden)?", "answers": ["$12.48", "$13.98", "$14.02", "$14.98"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}, {"question": "What is the price on a Hoverboard?", "answers": ["$200", "$250", "$275", "$300"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 3}, {"question": "How much does a 3D printer cost?", "answers": ["$400", "$600", "$800", "$1000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}, {"question": "What would you have to pay for a solar panel kit?", "answers": ["$750", "$800", "$1200", "$1000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 3}, {"question": "How much does a month of Netflix subscription cost?", "answers": ["$12.49", "$13.99", "$15", "$16"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 2}, {"question": "What is the price on a gourmet meal at a Michelin-starred restaurant?", "answers": ["$250", "$260", "$280", "$300"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 0}, {"question": "How much does a year's worth of Spotify premium cost?", "answers": ["$100", "$120", "140", "$159.99"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}, {"question": "What do you have to pay for a trip to the Maldives (for a week)?", "answers": ["$2500", "$5000", "$6750", "$7000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}, {"question": "How much does a set of professional golf clubs cost?", "answers": ["$500", "$1000", "$2500", "$3000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 2}, {"question": "How much does a fine bottle of wine cost?", "answers": ["$150", "$160", "$170", "$180"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 0}, {"question": "How cheap can you buy a drivable Ferrari 360 Modena for?", "answers": ["$50000", "$60000", "$75000", "$100000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 2}, {"question": "What can you buy a pair of noise-cancelling headphones for?", "answers": ["$80", "$400", "$250", "$300"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 3}, {"question": "How much is a Google stock worth right now? (5/5-2024)", "answers": ["$142.9", "$172.31", "$176.33", "$189.23"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 2}, {"question": "How much is NOT the parking ticket fine (in Sweden)?", "answers": ["$75", "$37.5", "$56.25", "$100"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 3}, {"question": "How much is a basic website worth?", "answers": ["$500", "$1000", "$1250", "$2000"], "user_answer": 0, "correct_answer_index": 1}]